ASTA REMEIKIENE

Phone: 07460581590 | Email: <u>asta.rem777@gmail.com</u> | Coventry LinkedIn: <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in</u>/asta-rem-developer/

Portfolio: https://astarem.github.io/react-portfolio/ | Github: https://github.com/AstaRem

PERSONAL PROFILE

Motivated, ambitious, and career-driven individual with strong communication skills gained throughout my professional journey.

With a background in transportation and logistics, I have gained a passion for web development. Currently, I am in the final stages of completing the Skills Bootcamp in Front-End Web Development & UX.

I am a fast learner who is enthusiastic about applying my skills and experiences. I am committed to embrace a lifelong journey of learning and growth.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Birmingham University & edX

Skills Bootcamp in Front-End Web Development & UX

2023 February - current

Codecademy

Full-stack Engineer

2021 September - 2022 May

2020 January - February

JBC Skills Training

City & Guilds Level 2 Diploma in ICT

City & Guilds Level 2 Diploma in ICT systems and Principles

PROJECTS

Stay Explorer | https://github.com/AstaRem/travel-app | https://astarem.github.io/travel-app/

- Summary: Hotel finding app
- Role: Group project
- Tools: JavaScript, CSS, HTML, third party APIs, local storage

Weather App | https://github.com/AstaRem/weather-app | https://astarem.github.io/weather-app/

- Summary: Weather forecast for 5 days in chosen location
- Role: Sole author
- Tools: JavaScript, CSS, HTML, third party API, local storage

Work day planner | https://github.io/workday-planner-app | https://astarem.github.io/workday-planner-app/

- Summary: Save day tasks in the list
- Role: Sole author
- Tools: JavaScript, CSS, HTML, local storage

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- JavaScript, React, Node.js, Bootstrap, jQuery, CSS, HTML
- GitHub, VS Code, Figma
- Familiar with Python, UI design, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, InDesign

OTHER KEY SKILLS

- Multi-lingual: Fluent in English, Lithuanian & Russian
- Taking ownership of my work
- Ability to meet deadlines and follow instructions if needed
- Excellent problem-solving skills
- Self-motivated and eager to learn
- Excellent communicator
- Efficient team collaborator
- Driving license and car owner

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Waterstones, Café W | Barista, part-time | 2022 December - current

Responsibilities:

- Preparing coffees and teas, hot food
- Serving customers at the front and perform back-end coffee shop duties
- Serving customers at the till

Shell Energy | Broadband Technical Adviser | 2022

Responsibilities included:

- Answering inbound calls from Broadband customers
- Resolving Broadband technical issues via the phone
- Using Zendesk and other software to log and update customer data
- Focusing on first contact resolution

Industrial Temporaries | Warehouse Operative | 2020-2022

Responsibilities included:

- Processing returns of DVD's, blue-rays, box sets and books using an in-house system
- All aspects of quality control
- Sorting and stacking items according to different brand requirements

CDW Ltd | Inventory Coordinator | 2015-2019

Responsibilities included:

- Working as part of the Inventory Control Team, resolving email requests regarding stock
- Using the in-house software system
- Resolving problems regarding booking in errors
- Filling in and running reports using Excel
- Ensuring bonded stock is kept in line with company requirements by monitoring expiry dates
- Managing the inventory of computer related goods desktops, laptops, tablets, servers, switches, kiosks, variety of cables, etc
- Checking goods onto the computerised systems and ensuring a high level of accuracy at all times

Staffline Group Plc | Industrial Operative | 2014-2015

Responsibilities included:

- Working at Tesco grocery warehouse, picking and packing wine products
- Packing and labelling groceries
- Quality control
- Using wearable computer (wrist scanner) and in-house software

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

I enjoy creative and challenging hobbies such as coding, learning surface pattern design using both hand drawing and software Adobe Illustrator and Photoshop. I also enjoy knitting and photography.